Press Gang Printers fonds
Simon Fraser University Archives and Records Management Department
- Correspondence and subject files, 1970 - 1992; F-134-4; 52 cm of textual records
  - Women's Collective Press (newspaper), 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Women's Collective Press, vol. 1 no. 8, April 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item118.
    - Women's Collective Press, vol. 2 no. 2, October 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item119.
    - Women's Collective Press, vol. 2 no. 3, November 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item120.
    - Women's Collective Press, vol. 2 no. 4, November 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item121.
    - Women's Collective Press, vol. 2 no. 5, December 1975; F-134-4-0-0-106-5 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item122.
  - Women's Conference Institute, 1979; F-134-4-0-0-107 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women's issues, 1978 - 1980; F-134-4-0-0-108 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women's Movement Archives, 1981; F-134-4-0-0-109 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Women's movement leaflets, 1979; F-134-4-0-0-110 (Archival box - standard 134-12)
  - Yellow Journal (newspaper), 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Yellow Journal, vol. 1 no. 1, April 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item123.
    - Yellow Journal, vol. 1 no. 7, 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item124.
    - Yellow Journal, vol. 1 no. 8, 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item125.
    - Yellow Journal, vol. 1 no. 8, 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item126.
    - Yellow Journal, vol. 1 no. 9, October 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-5 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item127.
    - Yellow Journal - Rage, vol. 1, October 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-6 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item128.
    - Yellow Journal - Rage, vol. 1, October 1970; F-134-4-0-0-111-7 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item129.
  - York University Women's Collective: Breakthrough (magazine), 1976; F-134-4-0-0-112 (Newspaper box 134-30)
    - Breakthrough: A York Feminist Magazine, vol. 2 no. 3, July 1976; F-134-4-0-0-112-1 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item130.
    - Breakthrough: A York Feminist Magazine, vol. 2 no. 4, October 1976; F-134-4-0-0-112-2 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item131.
    - Breakthrough: A York Feminist Magazine, vol. 2 no. 5, December 1976; F-134-4-0-0-112-3 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item132.
    - Breakthrough: A York Feminist Magazine, vol. 3 no. 1, February 1977; F-134-4-0-0-112-4 (Newspaper box 134-30)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item133.
  - Coyote Howls, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-113 (Newspaper box 134-29)
    - Coyote Howls, vol. 3 no. 2, 1976; F-134-4-0-0-113-1 (Newspaper box 134-29)
      Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item32.
- Production files, 1973 - 1993; F-134-5; 32 cm of textual records 12 printing plates
  Series consists of records relating to the printing operations of Press Gang Printers. Activities, events and topics documented include job tracking (by date and by client), management of equipment, printing policies and rates, and training. Records include registers and log books, customer cards, correspondence, reports, training grant applications and other forms, and a presentation on offset lithography.
  For other samples of Press Gang printing work, see series 6, "Printing samples."
  - Basic principles of offset lithography, [198-?]; F-134-5-0-0-1
  - Customer register, vol. 1, 1982 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-2 (Archival box - standard 134-13)
  - Customer register, vol. 2, 1982 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-3 (Archival box - standard 134-13)
  - Customer register, vol. 3, 1982 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-4 (Archival box - standard 134-13)
  - Job book, 1974; F-134-5-0-0-5 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Job docket register book, 1980 - 1991; F-134-5-0-0-6 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Job dockets, 1982; F-134-5-0-0-7 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Job estimates book, 1974 - 1975; F-134-5-0-0-8 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Job estimates book, 1979 - 1991; F-134-5-0-0-9 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Job register, 1991 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-10 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Log book, 1978; F-134-5-0-0-11 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - New plateburner, 1988; F-134-5-0-0-12 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Offset Workshop (OFY), 1975; F-134-5-0-0-13 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Plates, 1981 - 1982; F-134-5-0-0-14
  - Pre-press book, 1980 - 1981; F-134-5-0-0-15 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Production correspondence, 1973 - 1974; F-134-5-0-0-16 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - Production correspondence, 1990 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-17 (Archival box - standard 134-14)
  - [Rates and policies book], 1983 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-18 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
  - [Suppliers book], 1990 - 1993; F-134-5-0-0-19 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
  - Training and interview questions, 1989; F-134-5-0-0-20 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
  - Training - Canada Manpower industrial training, 1976 - 1982; F-134-5-0-0-21 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
  - Training - women in non-traditional work, 1983 - 1984; F-134-5-0-0-22 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
- Printing samples, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6; 1.64 m of graphic material 32 photographs 13 printing plates; Physical description: 15 photographs located in F-134-6-2-0-29 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-134-6-4-0-32 Physical description: 1 photograph located in F-134-6-4-0-110 Physical description: 3 photographs located in F-134-6-4-0-124 Physical description: 2 photographs located in F-134-6-4-0-162 Physical description: 9 photographs located in F-134-6-4-0-145
  Press Gang Printers kept a sample copy of virtually all materials that it printed. This series consists of the retained samples and includes buttons, cards, calendars, stickers, leaflets and brochures, newsletters, newspapers, booklets and other publications, and posters.
  The series was arranged by the archivist into sub-series based on document type in order to facilitate access and storage of the material.
  Periodicals have been described at the item level.
  For other material relating to printing operations generally, see series 5, "Production files."
  The files are open with no restrictions.
  - Printing samples - general, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1; 11 cm of textual records 11 cm of graphic material
    Sub-series consists of sample copies of buttons, cards, calendars, and stickers printed by Press Gang Printers.
    - Business cards, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-1 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
    - Buttons, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-2 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
    - Calendars, vol. 1, 1974 - 1989; F-134-6-1-0-3 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
    - Calendars, vol. 2, 1974 - 1989; F-134-6-1-0-4 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
    - Calendars, vol. 3, 1974 - 1989; F-134-6-1-0-5
    - Cards, vol. 1, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-6 (Archival box - standard 134-15)
    - Cards, vol. 2, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-7 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
    - Cards, vol. 3, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-8 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
    - Cards, vol. 4, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-9 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
    - Cards, vol. 5, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-10 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
    - Stickers, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-11 (Archival box - standard 134-16)
    - Stickers - bumper stickers, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-1-0-12
  - Leaflets, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-2; 38 cm of textual records 32 cm of graphic material 15 photographs
    Sub-series consists of sample copies of leaflets and brochures printed by Press Gang Printers.
    - Leaflets, 1972 - 1973; F-134-6-2-0-1 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1974 - 1975; F-134-6-2-0-2 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1976 - 1977; F-134-6-2-0-3 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1978; F-134-6-2-0-4 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1979; F-134-6-2-0-5 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1980; F-134-6-2-0-6 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1981; F-134-6-2-0-7 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, 1982; F-134-6-2-0-8 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, vol. 1, 1983; F-134-6-2-0-9 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, vol. 2, 1983; F-134-6-2-0-10 (Archival box - standard 134-17)
    - Leaflets, vol. 3, 1983; F-134-6-2-0-11 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1984; F-134-6-2-0-12 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1985; F-134-6-2-0-13 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1986; F-134-6-2-0-14 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1987; F-134-6-2-0-15 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1988; F-134-6-2-0-16 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1989; F-134-6-2-0-17 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1990; F-134-6-2-0-18 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1991; F-134-6-2-0-19 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets, 1992 - 1993; F-134-6-2-0-20 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 1, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-21 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 2, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-22 (Archival box - standard 134-18)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 3, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-23 (Archival box - standard 134-19)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 4, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-24 (Archival box - standard 134-19)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 5, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-25 (Archival box - standard 134-19)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 6, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-26 (Archival box - standard 134-19)
    - Leaflets - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 7, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-2-0-27 (Archival box - standard 134-19)
    - Leaflets - not dated, with union label, 1989 - 1993; F-134-6-2-0-28 (Archival box - standard 134-19)
    - Photographs, 1972 - 1993; F-134-6-2-0-29 (Archival box - small 134-33)
      15 photographs
  - Posters, 1970 - 1993; F-134-6-3; 8 cm of textual records 7 cm of graphic material
    Sub-series consists of sample copies of posters printed by Press Gang Printers.
    - Posterboards, 1970 - 1980; F-134-6-3-0-1
    - Posters, 1970 - 1977; F-134-6-3-0-2
    - Posters, 1978 - 1983; F-134-6-3-0-3
    - Posters, 1984 - 1988; F-134-6-3-0-4
    - Posters, 1989 - 1993; F-134-6-3-0-5
    - Posters - newsprint, 1970 - 1980; F-134-6-3-0-6
    - Posters - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 1, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-3-0-7
    - Posters - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 2, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-3-0-8
    - Posters - not dated, pre-union label, vol. 3, 1970 - 1989; F-134-6-3-0-9
  - Publications, 1971 - 1992; F-134-6-4; 1.07 m of textual records 1.07 m of graphic material 17 photographs
    Sub-series consists of sample copies of newsletters, newspapers, booklets and other publications printed by Press Gang Printers.
    Files are arranged alphabetically by the name of the organization or person publishing the material.
    - A Woman's Place Collective: A Vancouver Women's Health Booklet, 1972; F-134-6-4-0-1 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Aboriginal Support Committee, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-2 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Adult Basic Education Association of British Columbia: Groundwork, 1981 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-3 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - American Association of Physicians for Human Rights: Proceedings, 1985; F-134-6-4-0-4 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Around Kitsilano (newspaper), 1973; F-134-6-4-0-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Around Kitsilano, July 1973; F-134-6-4-0-5-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item134.
      - Around Kitsilano, August 1973; F-134-6-4-0-5-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item135.
    - Association for Women in the Justice System, 1978; F-134-6-4-0-6 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Association of Book Publishers of British Columbia: Signature, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-7 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Association of British Columbia Teachers of English as an Additional Language, 1982; F-134-6-4-0-8 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Association of University and College Employees, 1974 - 1980; F-134-6-4-0-9 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Association of University and College Employees: Across Campus, AUCE Local 1, UBC Newsletter, 1974 - 1975; F-134-6-4-0-10 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 2 no. 15, November 1974; F-134-6-4-0-10-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item136.
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 2 no. 16, December 1974; F-134-6-4-0-10-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item137.
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 3 no. 1, February 1975; F-134-6-4-0-10-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item138.
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 3 no. 2, March 1975; F-134-6-4-0-10-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item139.
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 3 no. 2, March 1975; F-134-6-4-0-10-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item140.
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 3 no. 4, April 1975; F-134-6-4-0-10-6 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item141.
      - Across Campus (AUCE 1), vol. 3 no. 4, April 1975; F-134-6-4-0-10-7 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item142.
    - Association of University and College Employees: AUCE Anchor, 1974 - 1976; F-134-6-4-0-11 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - AUCE Anchor (AUCE 2), vol. 1 no. 2, March 1974; F-134-6-4-0-11-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item143.
      - AUCE Anchor (AUCE 2), vol. 1 no. 2, March 1974; F-134-6-4-0-11-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item144.
      - AUCE Anchor (AUCE 2), August 1976; F-134-6-4-0-11-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item145.
    - Association of University and College Employees: AUCE Provincial News, 1977; F-134-6-4-0-12 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - AUCE Provincial News, vol. 2 no. 5, March 1977; F-134-6-4-0-12-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item146.
    - Autonomy News Service: BC Blackout, vol. 1, 1979 - 1987; F-134-6-4-0-13 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Autonomy News Service: BC Blackout, vol. 2, 1979 - 1987; F-134-6-4-0-14 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - B. K. S. Iyengar Yoga Association: Yoga Vancouver, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-15 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Battered Women's Support Services Newsletter, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-16 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - Bread News, [197-?]; F-134-6-4-0-17 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - British Columbia Civil Liberties Association: Discrimination: How Human Rights Laws Protect You, 1979; F-134-6-4-0-18 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - British Columbia Coalition of the Disabled: Transition, 1984 - 1989; F-134-6-4-0-19 (Archival box - standard 134-20)
    - British Columbia Deaf Advocate, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-20 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - B.C. Deaf Advocate, vol. 1 no. 4, November 1976; F-134-6-4-0-20-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item147.
    - British Columbia Federation of Women, 1976 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-21 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Federation of Women Newspaper, 1974 - 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 1, November 1974; F-134-6-4-0-22-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item148.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 2, January 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item149.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 2, January 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item150.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 3, February 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item151.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 3, February 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item152.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 4, March 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-6 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item153.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, April 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-7 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item154.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, April 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-8 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item155.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 7, June 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-9 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item156.
      - B.C. Federation of Women, vol. 1 no. 7, June 1975; F-134-6-4-0-22-10 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item157.
    - British Columbia Law Union: Directory, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-23 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Multicultural Health Coalition: Proceedings of the Multicultural Health Symposium, February 1989; F-134-6-4-0-24 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Organization to Fight Racism: Newsletter, 1981; F-134-6-4-0-25 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Regional Gay and Lesbian Conference, 1987 - 1988; F-134-6-4-0-26 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Speech and Hearing Association: Vibrations, 1981 - 1982; F-134-6-4-0-27 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Task Force on Immigrant Women: Immigrant Women in Canada, 1982; F-134-6-4-0-28 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Women's Sector tour to Nicaragua, 1986; F-134-6-4-0-29 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - British Columbia Women's Studies Association Newsletter, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-30 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - B.C. Women's Studies Association, vol. 1 no. 3, 1975; F-134-6-4-0-30-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item158.
    - Burnaby Tenants' Association: The Notice, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-31 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - The Notice: Burnaby Tenants Association, vol. 2 no. 1, March 1973; F-134-6-4-0-31-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item159.
    - Burnaby Tenants' Association: The Notice - photographs, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-32 (Archival box - small 134-33)
    - Byrne, Edward: Aporia, 1989; F-134-6-4-0-33 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - C-Tec: Microcomputers and Housing Co-ops, 1982; F-134-6-4-0-34 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Canada China Friendship Association Newsletter, 1971 - 1979; F-134-6-4-0-35 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, 1971; F-134-6-4-0-35-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item160.
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, vol. 4 no. 2, April 1973; F-134-6-4-0-35-2 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item161.
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, vol. 4 no. 3, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-35-3 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item162.
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, vol. 4 no. 3, June 1973; F-134-6-4-0-35-4 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item163.
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, vol. 4 no. 4, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-35-5 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item164.
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, vol. 4 no. 4, September 1973; F-134-6-4-0-35-6 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item165.
      - Canada-China Friendship Association, vol. 5 no. 1, March 1974; F-134-6-4-0-35-7 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item166.
      - Canada-China: Pan-Canadian Edition, vol. 1 no. 1, January 1979; F-134-6-4-0-35-8 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item167.
    - Canadian Association of Sexual Assault Centres: National Newsletter, vol. 1, 1971 - 1980; F-134-6-4-0-36 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - Canadian Association of Sexual Assault Centres: National Newsletter, vol. 2, 1971 - 1980; F-134-6-4-0-37 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - Canadian Brotherhood of Railway, Transport and General Workers, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-38 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - Canadian Coalition for Nuclear Responsibility: CCNR Newsletter, 1978 - 1979; F-134-6-4-0-39 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - Charter of Rights Coalition (B.C.): Women's Equality and the Charter of Rights and Freedoms, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-40 (Archival box - standard 134-21)
    - Chin-Yuen, Loy: The Book of the Heart, 1988; F-134-6-4-0-41 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Clerical Research Group, 1988; F-134-6-4-0-42 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Coalition Against the Marcos Dictatorship: Taliba News Flash / Commentary, 1980 - 1983; F-134-6-4-0-43 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Collins Bay Action Group: Earth Communique, 1985; F-134-6-4-0-44 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Committee for Democratic Unionism: The Spark, 1982; F-134-6-4-0-45 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Communitas, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-46 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Communitas, vol. 1 no. 2, 1974; F-134-6-4-0-46-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item168.
    - Community Congress for Economic Change Credit Union: CCEC Newsletter, 1979 - 1987; F-134-6-4-0-47 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Concerned Citizens for Choice on Abortion, 1979 - 1981; F-134-6-4-0-48 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Congress of Canadian Women: News, 1984; F-134-6-4-0-49 (Archival box - standard 134-22)
    - Consumer Resource Service, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-50 (Newspaper box 134-31)
      - Consumer Resource Service, 1973; F-134-6-4-0-50-1 (Newspaper box 134-31)
        Previous reference code assigned by SFU Archives: F-134-item169.